what's up my people first of all good
qué pasa mi gente antes que nada buenas
evening good evening let's see you know
noches buenas noches a ver ya sabéis que
I'm not making many videos well
no estoy haciendo muchos vídeos buena
maybe you haven't noticed it you haven't
vez no lo habéis notado no lo habéis
noticed because I had a lot of videos
notado porque tenía muchos vídeos el fin
last weekend from recording many
de semana pasado desde grabar muchos
videos on the main channel so that it wouldn't be
vídeos por canal principal para que no
too noticeable but of course there's already been
se notase mucho pero claro ya ha habido
a little boy here and it's that I have to
aquí un varoncito y es que tengo que
rest because we're not doing any
descansar porque es que no estamos de
work at home well it's not that
obra en casa bueno no es que esté
I'm doing the work there are no bricklayers
haciendo yo la obra no hay albañiles
here I don't know why or even put in a plug
aquí yo no sé por qué ni poner enchufe
but this morning with the
siquiera pero esta mañana con los
bricklayers looking I look like an
albañiles mirando parezco una persona
older person because I put
mayor del top porque yo me pongo a sí
myself you're not even behind me I go to the kitchen
misma ni estás atrás me voy a la cocina
and I start looking at the work and hey there it
y me pongo a mirar como a la obra y oye
hit me awake and of course in the
hay me pegó despierto y claro ya por la
afternoon well I don't have time to dedicate myself to
tarde pues no me da tiempo a dedicarme a
anything I don't know what there is still salt or powerful
nada no sé que hay aún sal se o potente
that there is to comment that I can't
que haya que comentar que no lo pueda
feel this that I see that is worth it
sentir esto que yo veo que merece la
on the secondary channel or a
en el canal secundario o una cara
main face well I don't think that this week I'm
principal pues no creo que esta semana
going to be quite absent for this
voy a estar bastante ausente para esta
little week I will be quite absent because
semanita estaré bastante ausente porque
I'm missing hours in the day okay  in
que me faltan horas en el día vale de
fact look I have a microwave here which I
hecho mira tengo un microondas aquí que
think I already said this is more than a
creo que ya lo dije este más que un
microwave and it's the only thing I have
microondas y es lo único que tengo
because in the kitchen
porque la cocina
right now I have to be at
ahora mismo tengo que estar en casa de
my father's house eating anyway
mi padre comiendo en fin
a little bird told me well what I saw
me ha dicho un pajarito bueno lo visto
on twitter a little bird told me that it does
en twitter me ha dicho un pajarito que
n't use you already upload a video about what
no te emplea ya sube un vídeo sobre qué
about the case they saw car a video is
sobre el caso vieron auto un vídeo
not there just a video in author place
no está sólo un vídeo en autor place
about
sobre
about what the [ __ ] it doesn't come out to me about inhabit
sobre qué [__] no me sale sobre
inhabiting totally about town it
habitan habitando totalmente sobre town
doesn't come out to me
no me sale a mí
a la carte from al asad even if well
a la carta de al asad aun si bueno
precisely there's no need for us to see the
precisamente no hace falta que veamos el
psychic because precisely what I
vidente porque yo precisamente lo que
had planned here to read is that
tenía aquí previsto para leer es esa
letter I mean I have it planned here the
carta o sea la tengo aquí prevista el
twitter code for my sign and I'm going to
código del twitter de mi signo y la voy
read it why because it's as if it goes on
a leer por qué pues porque es como si va
saying on twitter I saw that Dallas
diciendo en twitter he visto que dallas
recorded what will be an interview I
ha grabado lo que será una entrevista me
imagine what an interview will be Rafa
imagino lo que será una entrevista rafa
thank you very much with the girls with the
muchas gracias con las chicas con las
supposed victims of town okay
supuestas víctimas de town vale
Dallas is by the 30 posts he seems
dallas es por los 30 puestos se le ve
very confident and he's blaming tied I
muy seguro y está culpando atado
don't know what the hell it is that he saw I
no sé qué [__] será lo que ha visto yo
didn't ask him  I promise I'm
no le preguntamos lo prometo que estoy
really busy this week and I've barely
esta semana muy liado y apenas he
spoken to anyone but man Dallas has
hablado con nadie pero hombre dallas ha
been a person who has had a really
sido una persona que la ha pasado muy
bad time with false accusations I understand
mal con acusaciones falsas yo entiendo
that he's not going to catch on he was going to give
que que no va a [__] iba a darle
credibility to anything any [ __ ]
credibilidad a nada a cualquier [__]
you know so let's wait for the video
sabes entonces vamos a esperar el vídeo
to give it to see who's going to release it
de darla a ver quién lo que va a sacar
but to put it into context
pero para poner un poco en contexto
Dallas in the past I don't know exactly
dallas en el pasado no sé exactamente en
what year because look back in 2015
qué año porque a mira allá por el 2015
around here my sign had problems with this
por aquí mi signo tuvo problemas con
tan had problems with this state
este tan tuvo problemas con este estado
and let's read this letter that
y vamos a leer esta carta que le dedicó
Dallas dedicated to Town he never dedicated a video to him
dallas a town nunca le dedicó un vídeo
okay he never takes him to dedicate a video
vale nunca le lleva a dedicar un vídeo
let's see the letter what was the deal
vamos a ver la carta cuál fue la movida
that you had okay I'm
que tuvieron vale
going to start writing not only for
voy a empezar escribiendo no solo para
you Town gameplay but for the entire
ti town gameplay sino para todo el
public since you've decided for the
público ya que como tú has decidido por
billionth time to insult me
mil millonésima vez insultarme
publicly
públicamente
apparently hey if we look for Town
al parecer oye si buscamos town
if we look for Town there would
si buscamos town
be something I'm going to
habría algo
be and addressed there such a thing would
voy a estar y abordado hay tal
be deleted
estaría borrado
but okay second of all he has publicly
pero bueno segunda las públicamente ya
insulted him many times
le insultó muchas veces
and I've been putting up with your normalities for a year
y llevo un año aguantando tus
without saying a word I think it's
normalidades sin decir ni mú creo que va
time to  for the first time in
siendo hora de por primera vez emite en
your [ __ ] life you get a sad
tu [__] vida obtengas una triste
response friend since it seems that you
respuesta amiga ya que parece que te
walk around thinking about me and talking about me
paseas pensando en mí y hablándole de mí
to all your friends and acquaintances let's
a todos tus amiguitos y conocidos
start with the fragment of the
empecemos por el fragmento de la
story in which you have no [ __ ]
historia en la que tú no tienes ni [__]
idea how to live you have no [ __ ] idea
idea de vivir no tienen ni [__] idea de
who I am you have no [ __ ] idea
quién soy no tienes ni [__] idea de
who my friends are you haven't
quiénes son mis amigos no te han
bothered to get to know me you don't know what the
molestado en conocerme no sabes cómo es
people around me are like in short you have
la gente que me rodea en definitiva
never seen a video of mine you don't have
jamás has visto un vídeo mío no tienen
the vaguest conception of what kind of
ni una vaga concepción de qué clase de
person I am and since last year in
persona soy y desde el año pasado en
public on your shitty twitter you have
público en tu twitter de [__] te has
started insulting me calling me everything and
puesto a insultarme a llamarme de todo y
everything because for the donations it makes me
todo porque por las donaciones me hace
thank you very much it has made me I would love I would
muchas gracias me ha hecho me encantaría
love there to be something I would
me encantaría que hubiese algo me
love there to be something and from here I
encantaría que hubiese algo y desde aquí
ask you all that if you can recover
os pido a todos que si podéis recuperar
if someone can recover tweets and
que si alguien puede recuperar tweets y
things from aitana de empleo about dallas
cosas de aitana de empleo sobre dallas
that has been deleted to
que tiene eliminada
send it to me whoever is in charge sees it and
que me lo mande quien mande lo ve y lo
we see it here live because it makes me
vemos aquí en directo porque me hace
laugh a lot to remember that live of
mucha gracia recordar aquel directo de
jordi white when he said look at
jordi white cuando dijo fijaros que
dallas even tied up  uncle tied that a
dallas incluso atado tío atado que un
piece of bread that doesn't bother anyone
cachito de pan que no se mete con nadie
even to town also wrote him a
hasta a town también le escribió una
letter like that a little bit of the
carta así como lo de un poco lo de
usual it's not like mint like that you can
siempre no es como menta así se le puede
say whatever nothing but if he gives the
decir lo que sea nada pero sí da la
answer so dallas is looking for
responde así es que dallas está buscando
controversy not
polémica no
accusing me of being a thief good actor
acusándome de que si ladron buen actor
for the issue of donations we
por el tema de las donaciones esto ya lo
have already talked about this many times here
hemos hablado muchas veces aquí en
live what today is seen as normal
directo lo que hoy en día se ve normal
the fact that followers give you
el hecho de que los seguidores te den
gifts in the form of life in the form of
regalos en forma de vida en forma de
like the like in the case of you know in the
like the like en el caso de you know en
form of paypal that we also
el en forma de paypal que también
receive donations through paypal the
recibimos donaciones por paypal la
membership there are people that for all of me who are
membresía hay gente que por todos los
members well it is a form of
que soy miembro pues es una forma de
donation too that back in 2015
donación también eso por allá por 2015
here in Spain as we are always
aquí en españa como vamos siempre con
late it may be frowned upon they cannot
retraso puede estar como mal visto no
ask for donations or in other words
pueden pedir donaciones o sea que
esquerra is asking for donations and
esquerra está pidiendo donaciones y
begging for alms from people and today it
pidiendo limosna a la gente y hoy en día
is normalized
está normalizado
in fact well
de hecho bueno
all streamers live off
todos los streamer viven de las
donations
donaciones
tweets of 120 where youtube from
tweets del 120 donde youtube de donde
wherever but what does it do is another form
sea pero qué es lo que hace es una forma
of financing and no  there's
más de financiación y no tiene
absolutely nothing wrong with it, I'm
absolutamente nada de malo yo estoy
sure that all of you who are here, well,
seguro que todos los que estáis bueno
a large part of the people who
que una gran parte de la gente que la
are here, well in fact, town today I
que estáis aquí bueno de hecho town hoy
saw that he was in [ __ ], he didn't
he visto que estaba en la [__] no
have 600 viewers today in a live show
tenía 600 espectadores hoy en un directo
and he's abandoning him
y le está abandonando
since he has to stick his
ya que el mismo se tiene que meter la
tongue out his ass but I'm sure that
lengua del culo pero yo estoy seguro que
a lot of the people who are
es muchísima gente de las que estáis
here live right now
aquí en el directo ahora mismo
are subscribed to Netflix, Disney
estáis suscritas a netflix a disney
Blast or some entertainment platform
blast o alguna plataforma de
if it's in your favor scammer but now that you've
si está favor timador pero ahora que le
left him now that I've left them
has dejado ahora que las he dejado
being honest because I don't need them
siendo honesto porque ya no las necesito
there you have shut up it's something of an
ahí sí que te has callado es algo casa
envious dog house that you hide under
de perro envidioso que ocultas debajo de
all that beard let's not continue
toda esa barba no
with when I joined the tgn net when they added me to the skype group for vip members the little number of immature and mentally [ __ ] children that amount only because tgn signs me, I mean apparently according to equity account the managers of tgn which is a network against the article
en contra del artículo
these people have one in which in the
esta gente tener una en el cual en la
same network is  tgn where
misma network es tgn donde también
fernando flor was also watching gamer
estaba fernando flor ver gamer
the cousin from town and apparently he had
el primo de town y al parecer pues tenía
a group live on skype and when
un grupo vive en el skype y cuando
they put dallas in then down the mess I'm
metieron a dallas pues down la lío yo me
out if he comes from dallas I know if on
salgo si viene de dallas yo me sé si
top of gender with the ally
encima de género con la aliada que
we had an author and I counted January
tuvimos un autor y yo conté enero
and I still have screenshots how good it would be to get
y aún guardo capturas que bueno sería
all this out and anwar two
que dar la sacarse todo esto y anwar dos
screenshots because what I was laughing my
capturas porque lo que me estuve
ass off with your mental retardation
partiendo el culo con tu retraso mental
has no name you go and say I'm leaving and you
no tiene nombre vas y dices me voy y te
go alone because I have arrived and
pidas únicamente porque he llegado yo y
with you your friend the verse that I think
contigo a tu amigo el verso que creo que
his cousin is really another one with another one
su primo en verdad otro que con otro más
with whom I have never spoken in my [ __ ] life
con el que no he hablado en mi [__] vida
and I also know that all kinds
y también sé que va saltando toda clase
of [ __ ] is jumping about me just from his part the
de [__] sobre mí sólo por su parte la
dick with both hands to you
[__] a dos manos a ti
and if you think I'm stupid and all the
y si te crees que soy tonto y toda la
people you talk bad about me don't
gente a la que le hablas mal de mí no me
come to me later tell me smarter I mean
viene después contármelo más listo o sea
watch game bears gamers it even has a
ver game bears gamers tiene incluso un
video it
vídeo
's great the channel bears gamer
está buenísimo el canal bears gamer
dallas even has a video  dallas
dallas tiene incluso un vídeo dallas
well the dog issue I ca
bien el tema perro
n't take it anymore I need to vent
no aguanto más necesito desahogarme
criticize the dallas
critica el juego de dallas
berger game messi has had several several
berger messi ha tenido varios varias
policies like in public she is
políticas en plan en público es
hired
contratada
because just like they have done now with
porque igual que han hecho ahora con
this girl who is not threatened that she
esta muchacha que no se ve amenazado la
is playing a follow because they
de que se está jugando un follow porque
say she likes my videos but her
dicen que le gustan mis vídeos pero su
son of a [ __ ]
hijo de [__]
[Laughs]
[Risas]
all day hugging
todo muchísimo el día abrazando a una a
a girl with giving her a follow because she said
una chica con darle un follow porque
she liked the videos
dijo que le gustaba los vídeos me
reminds me of when we were in a whatsapp group
recuerda cuando estábamos en un grupo de
me when in reality and a person said
yo cuando en realidad y una persona dijo
that the video of giving the daily of the
que el vídeo de dar las diarias del
video clip that was good and they kicked us out
videoclip que estaba bien y nos echaron
of the group sense areas of the group I don't believe
del grupo sense áreas del grupo no creo
what happened has been
que lo que pasó
threatening your friendship and
ha estado amenazando con tu amistad y
follow to other youtubers some
follow a otros youtubers algunos
helped by your mentally [ __ ] ass
ayudados de tu culo de [__] mental
others have eaten support me they told me in
otros han comido apoyan me han dicho en
an email I don't know if it will be true lie
un email no sé si será verdad mentira
that wish michu these days has given a
que wish michu en estos días ha dado un
follow to everyone
follow a todo
so if it will be true or not I have not
entonces si será verdad o no no lo he
checked but it makes me thank you very much and
comprobado pero me hace muchas gracias y
has given a follow to town and does not give
le ha dado un follow a town y no le da
a pole to another youtuber with the  how
un polo a otro youtuber con los que
good the [ __ ] he collaborated with the madman he's a
bueno [__] colaboró con el demente es
friend of cracker anyway
amigo de cracker en fin
tremendous hypocrites they all walk around chicha
tremendos hipócritas andan chicha todos
but what you and all your friends
pero lo que tú y todos tus amiguitos
have in common is that you are a bunch of
tenéis en común es que sois una panda de
envious sons of [ __ ] and why
envidiosos hijos de [__] y por qué
climates envy me I will tell you and I am sure
climas envidiar de mí os diré y seguro
that I beg you from there is that you have more
que os ruego de ahí es que tenéis más
visits than me we will clamor and between
visitas que yo ya vamos a clamar y entre
you that my channel is far behind
vosotros que mi canal se queda muy atrás
with respect to yours well I am I
con respecto al vuestro bueno estoy
am the tortilla it is that it is that it is that
estoy la tortilla es que es que
life has downloaded it's not that
es que la vida ha descargado no es que
life life takes many turns
la vida la vida da muchas vueltas la
life takes many turns let's see hay town
vida da muchas vueltas a ver hay town
gameplay
gameplay
man let's see it's that
hombre a ver
I have just flipped out because of
es que me acabo de que ha flipado porque
course the channel to have 12 million
claro el canal para tener 12 millones de
subscribers each individual video does not
suscriptores cada vídeo individual no es
have many visits what happens is that of
que tenga muchas visitas lo que pasa es
course as he uploads many videos in
que claro como sube muchos vídeos en bus
constant bus well the guy gets an average
constante pues el tío se hace una media
of two videos of visits a day
de dos vídeos de visitas al día
one video of visits a day 30 million
un vídeo de visitas al día 30 millones
a month is money it
al mes es pasta
is money
es pasta
depending on where the visit comes from it can
depende de donde venga la visita puede
be between 15,000 or  30,000 or
estar la cosa entre 15.000 ó 30.000 o
40,000 euros depends on where the
40.000 euros depende donde venga la
visit comes from. I think this guy has the
visita yo creo que este chaval la
majority of his audience Latino and they will be
mayoría de la audiencia tiene latina y
around 15,000 euros around there. But
rondarán los 15.000 euros por ahí pero
well,
bueno
Dallas is much better in comparison,
dallas en comparación está mucho mejor
honestly,
la verdad porque
because Dallas has like three million
porque dallas tiene como tres millones
fewer subscribers, let's say, and
menos de suscriptores digamos y sin
yet it has three channels.
embargo tiene tres canales
The main channel already has 4
en el canal principal ya tiene 4
million more visits than the one
millones más de visitas que el seguro
that is more monetized than the best. To
que mas monetizadas que el mejor
monetize, that one in Dallas without a filter
monetizar aquel en el dallas sin filtro
has 7 million visits,
pues tiene 7 millones de visitas
not insignificant, and in War the Game it
nada despreciables y en el war the game
has 3 million visits.
tiene 3 millones de visitas
Badri, we're
el badri
talking about
estamos estamos hablando de que sumamos
40 million visits, not 40, 40, and 43
40 millones de visitas no 40 40 y 43
million, if my calculations are correct, and from
millones si no me falla las cuentas y de
memory, 43 million visits, it's
memoria 43 millones de visitas está
better, we could say that life takes
mejor podríamos decir que la vida da
many turns and what I do today
muchas vueltas y qué hago hoy en día
is better, it's Dallas, this is how it is, I mean,
está mejor es dallas esto así es o sea
today I'm better than other
yo hoy estoy mejor que otros canales de
criticism channels that have a lot of
críticas que tienen mucho para
subscribers than me, and maybe at another
suscriptores que yo y a lo mejor en otro
time those channels have been better
momento esos canales han estado mejor
than me, tomorrow they will be better than
que yo mañana vuelven a estar mejor que
me again.  I have more subscribers than them
yo y yo tengo más suscriptores que ellos
and this is something that has to be
y esto es una cosa de la que haya que
made fun of like one thing is a joke
burlarse en plan una cosa es una coña
like when we do it on surman some
como cuando lo hacemos en surman alguna
joke and it feels bad but oh
bromita y que le sienta mal estado pero
well but one thing is a beer without
bueno pero una cosa una cañita sin
truth and another thing is laughing it makes you bitter not
verdad y otra cosa es reír te amarga no
since a channel is time to deal
desde que un canal es tiempo de tratar
because life takes many turns and
porque la vida da muchas vueltas y la
next week there is a video that
semana que viene toca un vídeo que te
blows you up and suddenly the channel gets up they understand me
peta y de repente el canal levanta me
and as I asked for the tweets
y como he pedido de los trinos
well they just sent me a tweet
pues me acaban de mandar un tweet
don't know if it's real or not because
no sé si sea real o no porque no lo
we can't verify it but come on I
podemos comprobar pero vamos yo me
imagine that if not I don't think it's
imagino que si no no creo que sea
fake but anyway just in case he
falsificado pero bueno por si acaso lo
left it in the air it
dejó en el aire
strikes me that he has the
me llama la atención que tiene puesta la
same photo posted as now when we
misma foto que ahora cuando nosotros
finish he does a search and as soon as they
acabamos hace una búsqueda y nomás nos
come in another tweet appears
van aparece otro tweet
look list he tells me the marble let's go see the
mira lista me dice el mármol vamos a ver
sea let's
mar
see more
a ver más
harmony are you talking
armóa estás hablando
marble
mármol
for the photo that I sent you from the middle
para la foto que te mandé de mitad
listen to me seriously dude
escúchame enserio churra
what am I telling you dude
qué te digo tío
from an hour saying but let's look
de una hora diciendo pero vamos a mirar
let's look at the photo of the
vamos a mirar la foto del tatuaje de
marble tattoo he said he has a  now saying
mármol dijo que lleva una hora diciendo
the young people who also really were
los jóvenes que también en verdad que
let's do the math damn let's see the
eran echamos cuentas [__] vamos a ver la
photo of the tattoo by the book what does it matter
foto del tattoo de manual que importa
now yours has put it
una [__] ahora lo tuya la haya puesto
since let's see what the marble is
el desde a ver cuál es el mármol
what does God matter and what the [ __ ] matters what
qué importa dios y qué [__] importa lo
the town has put on it that they prevent t
que le ha puesto el town que impiden t
who the [ __ ] knows him let's see where he is
quién [__] lo conoce a ver dónde está
sea death
mar muerte
bad an hour ago
mal hace una hora
where else my brother comes out to me
donde más mi hermano me sale
Manuel I don't see him
manuel no lo veo yo
tell me it's that
dime
we are here giving importance
es que estamos aquí dando la importancia
to [ __ ] destroys the wta put on the
a la [__] destruye la wta puesto en el
table that we don't care anymore we want to
tapete que no nos importa más queremos
see your drawing
ver tu dibujo
then we talk about it but as if we talked about it later
luego lo hablamos pero como que luego lo
badly
hablamos mal
like we talked about it later but with some
como que luego lo hablamos pero con unas
trays and now
bandejas y ahora
how are you going to leave us like this
como nos vas a dejar así
if we were all here
si estábamos todo el mundo aquí
pending and waiting for that an hour for
pendiente y esperando eso una hora para
nothing an hour
nada
for nothing
una hora para nada
well the case who was in charge the most ours and
bueno el caso que más mandaba nuestro y
no here there's one who says I don't like to
no aquí hay uno que dice no me gusta
give it to me it seems like garbage not only his
darle me parece basura no sólo sus
videos but also that of any other
vídeos sino también el de cualquier otro
tweet that says I can't have my
tweet que dice yo no puedo tener mi
opinion it enters us in the same one that they
opinión nos entra en el mismo a que
suck at the same seven times thank you
maman al mismo siete veces gracias
Roberto for sending me this email with
roberto por mandarme este email con
seven times the same that no longer me only the
siete veces mismo que ya no me nomás las
notifications have
notificaciones
not seen anything it is  I'm not going to
ya no vieron nada ya es que no voy a
do the math, I'm
echar cuentas
not going to do any more math than I
no voy a echar más cuenta que yo
really do, let's
de verdad
see,
a ver
but what you and all your friends
pero lo que tú y todos tus amiguitos
have in common is that you're a bunch of
tienen en común es que sois una panda de
envious sons of [ __ ],
envidiosos hijos de [__]
well, this is the thing about the
bueno esto es lo de la visita
obsessed visit with me to the point of utter disregard
obsesionada conmigo hasta la tranca
when I haven't done anything, I wasn't looking for
cuando ya no he hecho nada no te buscaba
any harm to you or any of
ningún mal ni para ti ni para ninguno de
your friends, but the quiet one keeps being a pain in the
tus amigos pero el tranquilo sigue
ass, keeps acting like a
tocando los [__] sigue haciendo el
[ __ ] [ __ ] idiot on twitter and
[__] imbécil [__] por el twitter y
spouting free [ __ ] about me, which might
soltando [__] gratuita de mí que igual
even have encouraged me to make a video
y hasta me animó a hacerte un vídeo
answering you, that way he'll give me family and you
respondiendo te así me da familia y te
can reaffirm your stupidity that I
puedes reafirmar en tu subnormalidad de
'm a fight seeker, but don't
que soy un busca peleas pero no te
forget to go around saying that I'm
olvides de ir diciendo por ahí que yo
looking for a fight when you've been
voy buscando pelea cuando llevan más de
enjoying yourself for over a year, I'm looking for a
un año disfrutando me llave busco pelea
free fight when you're the first
gratuita cuando tú eres el primer punto
[ __ ] [ __ ] who goes around spouting garbage about me
subnormal que va soltando basura de mí
and threatening people with
por ahí y amenazando a la gente con
unfriending them, although my videos are
dejar de ser su amigo si bien mis vídeos
one thing, who the [ __ ] did you think
una cosa tú quién [__] te has pensado
that your excessiveness, threatening
que tu desmesurado algo por amenazar a
people with that, is nothing more than a
la gente con eso no es más que el
reflection of the fact that you're a [ __ ] [ __ ]  loser gets on
reflejo de que eres un [__] perdedor se
top of me and I know that if you have so much
auto encima y sé que si me tienes tanto
irrational, excessive hate for me it's because you
odio desmesurado irracional es porque
know that I'm better than you, that I'm more
sabe que soy mejor que tú que soy más
handsome than you,
guapo que tú
whoever is good here and here would be
quien es bueno aquí y aquí sería estaría
good beauty pageant that
buenos desfile de belleza que
directly starts his egg god will
directamente se arma huevo suyo dios nos
leave us with [ __ ] and good
dejará de gilipolleces y de bueno
too that is not yours to live the fight is
también que no es tuyo a vivir la pelea
also already okay okay okay okay okay
también está ya vale vale vale vale vale
the fight 2000 you
la pelea 2000
're messing with me you
me estáis vacilando ya
're messing with me
me estáis vacilando
to live that I'm not going to sleep
a vivir de que que no me voy a dormir
or at least but what I finished
o por lo menos pero lo que terminé de
recording
grabar
now
ahora
because whoever commits another reading what you
porque quien cometa otro leando que me
're telling me everyone to me a thousand
estáis diciendo todo el mundo a mí mil
is a gift boomer
es un regalo boomer
a gift to live
un regalo a vivir
like a gift has lived you're
como hace un regalo ha vivido me estáis
sending me the little pill from the bed the
mandando la pastillita de la cama
little pill that they gave me 2000
la pastillita a que me dieron 2000
thank you very much to whoever gave it to me
muchas gracias a quien me la ha dado
and the caravia salt
y la sal caravia
and two to the point damn today everyone is
y dos al punto [__] ya hoy todo el
worth it and the very high damn
vale y los altísimo [__]
I'm here holding on because you
estoy aquí aguantando porque me habéis
gave me and 250,000 light otherwise I would take my
dado y 250.000 light sino que me bajaba
pants off now  I have it
el pantalón ahora mismo
alive I have a life of friendship
tengo viva mi tengo una vida de amistad
and sentimental much better than yours you already
y sentimental mucho mejor que la tuya ya
know about my girlfriend there are no videos and photos
saben de mi novia no hay vídeo y fotos
masturbating for money
masturbándose por dinero
this one comes
es esta que viene
made that comes
hecho que viene
and I let myself since Caracas is
y yo que me deje ya que caracas está
imposing in the chat me of living
imponiendo en el chat yo del vivir
and here is the chat
y aquí está el chat
or rather the woman of the town was a
o sea que la mujer de the town era
webcam he
webcam él
is a gift of 2000 thank you very much that
es un regalo de 2000 muchas gracias que
is a gift okay thank you I can't
es un regalo vale gracias yo no podéis
put 2000 and that's it you have to be
poner 2000 y ya está tenéis que estar
there with the living she
ahí con el vivir
is giving me
me está dando
[Music]
[Música]
nor did I meet her on a
ni tampoco la conocí en una página de
chat page urbe
chat urbe
so you know the next time you
así que ya sabes la próxima vez que me
want to criticize me better life you
quieras criticar mejor vida te a ti
yourself and when it's better is a little while she comes
mismo y cuando mejor es un ratito viene
and sucks my [ __ ] [ __ ]
y me chupas la [__] cabrón
better goodbyes than that there are
mejores despedidas que esa no hay
none off it
ninguna en off
went too far with the girlfriend well of
se pasó mucho con lo de la novia bueno
course I
es que claro
work totally ready each one can
trabajo totalmente listo cada uno puede
do with their body what they want if they
hacer con su cuerpo lo que quiera si
are there they don't have to mess with anyone what
está no tiene por qué meterse con nadie
happens is that of course we would have to
lo que pasa que claro
see we would have to see if good
habría que ver habría que ver si buena
creator way we should never involve the
creator manera no hay que meter nunca la
family I mean it's not only because of what
familia o sea ya no es solamente por lo
has insulted not only  for him for what
que ha insultado no solamente por él por
he has for what he has insulted him
lo que lo ha por lo que lo ha insultado
and the simple fact of including the girlfriend
y el simple hecho de meter a la novia no
is not to enjoy him and him and that's it you don't have to
sea disfrutarlo a él ya él y ya está no
include the girlfriend at all
tienes que meter a la novia para nada
but what happens is that we don't know what the hell it is that
pero lo que pasa es que no sabemos qué
he said the other one to him
[__] es lo que le dijo él el otro a él a
maybe the other one has also messed around
lo mejor el otro también se ha metido
as always with the sister the mother I don't
como siempre con la hermana la madre no
know what so right now seeing
sé qué entonces ahora mismo viendo
only this well I would say that the
solamente esto pues yo diría que todo el
rest of the letter is taken in the mouth
resto de la carta se la lleva en la boca
that the thing about the girlfriend was unnecessary in the case
que lo de la novia sobraba en el caso
that the other one hasn't messed around it's that
que el otro no se haya metido es que
even if the other one has messed around with his
aunque el otro se haya metido con su
family I think that you don't have to get into
familia yo creo que no tienes que entrar
the same thing do the same thing because
tú en lo mismo hacer lo mismo porque
then in the end it ends up being the same it
entonces al final acaba siendo lo mismo
's not like what when duros said that
no es como lo que cuando duros decía que
the page of trickery or co was justified
estaba justificado la página de ardid o
why have they sent you 22 thousand thanks let's
qué te han mandado 22 mil gracias
see what rain look at my egg let's see
a ver qué llover me mires en el huevo
that I'm going to live
a ver que yo voy a vivir
to put it
a ponerlo
[Music]
[Música]
something colder
cosa más fría
and 15 already drawn a while ago if it looks like a
y 15 ya dibujado hace rato si parece un
picture of my grandmother's house
cuadro de casa de mi abuela
and I am a woman here with whom the [ __ ] is it
y yo soy mujer aquí con quién [__]
drawn today  an or and it puts my child and
dibujado es hoy una o y pone a mi niño y
quietly scratching the thousand or
tranquilamente rayando mejor el mil o
so, what a shame that it is not recorded
sea qué pena que no se quede grabado
because the people of YouTube are not
porque la gente de youtube no se está
understanding, there is nothing that is happening
enterando hay nada lo que está pasando
but that painting,
pero ese cuadro
yes, a painting by Valero, I am not a gift
si cuadro de valero yo no es un regalo
again,
otra vez
what a cold thing about the painting
qué cosa más fría del cuadro
and on top of that it occupies the whole screen, I mean,
y encima ocupa toda la pantalla o sea
while it was the [ __ ] cat, I couldn't
que mientras que al ser el [__] gato no
see myself, it
me veía a mí
has a background, the background is still beautiful,
tiene trasfondo sigue precioso el
you are what the [ __ ] who
tú estás cuáles las [__] quién ha
made that drawing,
hecho ese dibujo
this direct time has passed
paso ya este directo tiempo
for Soria from this director
para soria de este director